Miss Song is no stranger to our family.
So in the future,
we might even become family.
Isn't that right?
Speaking of acquaintances,
my acquaintances in the Cheng family
aren't limited to just Cheng An.
Sang Luo,
it's been a few years.
I could hardly recognize you.
You two know each other?
When I first met Sang Luo,
I had no idea she was a Cheng.
I...
only recently returned to the Cheng family
and reclaimed my identity.
So,
have you been well these past few years?
What happened to your hand?
Got injured, but it's nothing serious.
Eldest daughter-in-law,
go check the kitchen.
See how the food is coming along.
Cheng Yan,
take Song Yun
for a walk in the courtyard.
Get to know each other better.
Okay.
I've looked into it.
Ten years ago, Song Yun went against her parents' wishes
and worked as a nurse for a year.
During that time,
Sang Luo happened to be in the hospital.
Got it.
As for the relationship between them,
it's still not very clear.
Since they're old acquaintances,
I'm afraid she won't be easy to deal with.
I just don't know if Song Yun is here for the marriage alliance,
or something else.
You don't need to worry about that.
I've already sent someone to look for
the former staff of Benevolence Hospital.
We should find some useful clues.
Actually, the root of this matter
lies with Cheng An and Cheng Yan.
They are competing against each other.
Otherwise, Song Yun alone
wouldn't be able to make waves.
Whether using a marriage alliance to keep his status,
or making a calculated move
to proactively cooperate,
he is profit-driven,
hypocritical,
and deceitful.
This is the real Cheng An.
This is all thanks to you Chengs.
This is what you all owe me.
They are clearly not the same person,
so why does she feel so familiar?
Are you free tomorrow?
I'd like to meet with you.
Anytime.
I didn't expect Sang Luo and the Song family
to have a connection.
Miss Song.
Wouldn't it be better to find a quiet place?
Why did you have to come to Valley Breeze?
The public is optimistic about the Cheng-Song marriage alliance.
To be prudent,
I need to understand
Valley Breeze Group's operations.
If we establish
a loveless business marriage alliance,
I will help you become
the sole heir of the Cheng family.
Then, Miss Song,
why did you choose me?
Compared to
Cheng Yan, whose scandals are everywhere,
Anxin Group needs a smart
and highly capable son-in-law.
You flatter me, Miss Song.
I know
Cheng Yan was instigated by Old Madam Cheng
and has been pestering you.
Rest assured,
leave this matter to me.
I knew I made the right choice.
All right.
I don't have any other questions.
Miss Song.
Wait a moment.
I have one last question.
Is your return to the country this time
because of Sang Luo?
That is my private matter.
Miss Song.
This way is the sales department.
Ahead is
the R&D department.
Wow.
Uncle and Miss Song are really a good match.
A perfect couple.
It seems
you've already accepted her as your aunt.
Don't worry, Aunt Lin.
I'm still on your side.
It's just that...
It's just that Uncle looks like
he's quite smitten with Miss Song.
That's quite nice.
Thank you for showing me around the company today.
I need to use the restroom first.
Excuse me.
My bracelet.
I've been looking for it for so long.
A very important friend of mine
gave it to me.
Returned to its rightful owner.
Do you still remember this bracelet?
Of course.
Sister Song Yun.
I didn't expect that after all these years,
you'd keep it in such good condition.
Yeah.
I remember when you were little,
you'd always call me Sister Song Yun.
I can't believe you're all grown up.
Yeah, exactly.
Our childhood days
were always so happy.
So carefree.
Do you know what the real Sang Luo
used to call me?
She never called me Sister Song Yun.
Instead, she called me
Sister Song.
I knew Sister Song
could definitely do it!
Is this for me?
I remember when you were little,
you had a unique birthmark.
Can I see it?
You're talking about this, right?
I was in an accident once.
I can't remember a lot of people and things.
After I got burned here,
the birthmark disappeared.
I didn't expect so many coincidences
and hardships to happen to you all at once.
When you were little,
you always loved chatting with me.
Why does it feel like now you're grown,
your words carry a hidden meaning?
Can a person's personality
really change?
It can,
Sister Song Yun.
Yeah.
People do change.
But some things
will never change.
How did you and Song Yun meet?
Aren't you being a bit too nosy?
Who I meet
and how long I've known them
is my own private business.
Or could it be
that you want to use me, Uncle,
to scout your marriage alliance partner?
You could say that.
What?
You really want a marriage alliance with her?
It seems I don't have any other choice.
Uncle,
you look so pathetic weighing the pros and cons.
Do you have a death wish?
How long has it been since your miscarriage?
What else can I do?
Old Madam Cheng wants a marriage alliance.
Whether it's Cheng An or Cheng Yan,
whoever marries Song Yun,
she will walk all over me.
If they find out I lost the baby,
I'll have nothing left.
You still have me.
Wanmei,
leave the Cheng family.
I can stay by your side forever.
No.
Even if it's for our child,
I absolutely cannot leave the Cheng family.
I absolutely cannot let Song Yun marry into the Cheng family.
Everything in the Cheng family...
I am determined to get it all.
Ms. Song!
I like you!
Will you be my girlfriend?
Mr. Yan,
I'm not interested in you.
Please step aside.
Song Yun!
Ever since I met you,
I finally know what love is,
and what makes my heart race.
Will you marry me?
Marry him!
No, no, no.
Ms. Song,
if you don't say yes,
I won't let you leave.
Yan!
What are you doing here?
What are you...
Who is this?
I don't know her!
Didn't you say I was the only one in your heart?
Cheng Yan!
You called me sweetie last night!
When did I...
And now you pretend not to know me?
Mr. Yan,
I think
you should clean yourself up first.
Don't waste my time.
I'm pretty clean!
Don't go!
Ms. Song!
Where are you going?
I...
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Mom! Mom! Stop hitting me!
Stop!
You can't do anything right!
You just ruin everything!
You ruined a perfectly good situation!
I was wrong.
I...
Mom,
I swear, that little model and I
are completely over!
I swear!
Mom.
I really messed up.
Help me figure out
what I should do next.
Do you think I'm like you,
panicking at the last minute?
Brilliant.
Mom,
what's the plan?
Oh, you...
Leak the news
and tell everyone
that Song Yun finally chose to marry you
and gave up on Cheng An.
Will that work?
Won't Song Yun tear me apart?
I've already spoken with Song Yun's stepmother.
Valley Breeze's chairman can only be you.
Song Yun will be the chairman's wife.
The more high-profile
you make this news,
the harder it will be
for the Song family to back out.
To save face,
she'll have to swallow this marriage.
High-profile...
High-profile.
Being high-profile is what I do best!
Remember
to go apologize to her.
Let her see your sincerity.
Got it, Mom.
Love you.
This is Song Yun's file.
She's highly suspicious by nature.
She won't let go of her doubts about you easily.
I know.
Then you'd better keep your distance from her.
As for the Cheng-Song marriage alliance,
we can figure out another way.
A single spark
can start a prairie fire.
Hurry up.
Why aren't you anxious at all?
Come here.
Sit down.
Help your Second Uncle choose.
Look at these.
The vintage one.
The modern one.
And this designer collaboration.
I don't even know what this stuff is.
Tell me.
Which one would Song Yun like?
Let me take a look.
Take a look.
She won't like any of them.
No way.
With things like these,
if I gave them to any other girl,
she'd be totally mesmerized.
Song Yun has seen it all.
Second Uncle.
Look at what you've picked.
Why would she like any of these?
What should I do then?
What Song Yun has always wanted
is your sincere heart, Second Uncle.
But instead,
you shoved your affair right in her face.
Who would've thought
Tripped up at the last minute?
That girl had to be so blind
to cling to me at such a crucial moment.
Little niece,
your Second Uncle has never been
this devoted to a girl.
Help your Second Uncle figure out a way.
How can I
turn this around?
You really want to marry her?
I really do.
You really want to marry into her family.
I'm dead set on it.
Who is the current head of the Song family?
Song Qingfeng.
Song Yun was called back by her father.
Since you can't win over Song Yun,
win over someone else instead.
Give these
to her father.
Tell me, tell me.
Song Yun's father loves antiques.
Second Uncle.
Think about it.
To catch the bandits, first catch their leader.
Exactly.
Brilliant, niece.
Got it.
I'll give these
to you.
Thank you, Second Uncle.
Sometimes I really don't understand.
Are you on my side
or Cheng Yan's side?
What good does it do me to help Cheng Yan?
Auntie Lin.
After all,
we are true family.
Cheng Yan came to you for help.
As expected,
nothing gets past you, Auntie Lin.
He begged me
to give him ideas
to win over Miss Song.
And you?
Are you going to help Cheng Yan marry Song Yun?
I think
Auntie Lin probably wants even less for my uncle
to get engaged to Song Yun.
Uncle Song.
This is
a little gift I prepared for you.
Just a small token of my respect.
I know
you have a deep knowledge of antiques.
These little trinkets
definitely won't catch your eye.
Therefore,
I also prepared this.
Please take a look.
Uncle Song,
I know
you're worried your precious daughter,
your Treasure, being wronged.
To be honest,
my romantic life over the years
has been full of dark clouds.
But ever since I met Song Yun,
she's been like a ray of sunshine,
melting my hardened heart.
My mother and I have discussed this.
As long as Song Yun is willing to marry me,
a portion of our shares
will be transferred to her name.
Does Old Madam Cheng know about this?
Of course.
My mother has nothing but praise for her.
Uncle,
this is something I asked a friend
to specially prepare: Kyara.
If you don't like it,
as the saying goes,
It's the thought that counts.
Dad.
Are you planning
to trade your daughter for these cheap beads?
Yun!
Back then, Aunt Zhao
seduced you over appreciating antiques,
driving my mother to her death.
What,
because of these cheap beads,
you'd sell your daughter to the Chengs?
You!
Are you trying to make me die of anger?
Uncle,
hit me if you're angry.
Don't hit Yun.
Only people with a conscience die of anger.
But looking at you two,
I don't see a shred of conscience.
As for this marriage,
whoever wants it can have it!
Yun!
You're marrying him whether you want to or not!
Cheng Yan,
your marriage is settled.
Thank you, Uncle.
Yan!
You're here!
Sit here.
I missed you so much.
Tonight,
drink up and have fun!
Drinks are on me!
Yeah!
Let's toast to Mr. Yan!
Cheers!
You're getting married,
so why are you here looking for me?
Just because I'm getting married,
does that mean you're not my little baby?
That woman from the Song family
is a total bore.
Unlike you.
You're always so much fun.
She's the only precious child of the Song family.
All the future fortune belongs to her.
Once I have her in my hands,
all this future fortune
will belong to me.
What are you so happy about?
Nothing.
Yucheng.
Give me another baby.
I need a baby.
No.
You're in Post-miscarriage confinement.
I can't let you hurt your body like this.
I don't care.
But I do.
If you care about me,
just give me what I want.
Right now.
The Cheng and Song families
are highly influential in business.
We have always adhered to
the philosophy of integrity and progress.
The two families
are united by our children's bond.
This can be considered a perfect match,
an alliance of well-matched families.
Now,
I officially announce...
That woman from the Song family
is a total bore.
Look!
Isn't that Director Yan?
Who did this?!
Turn it off!
Stop filming! Stop filming!
Stop filming!
all this future fortune
will belong to me!
Yun, you have to believe me!
It's all fake!
It's corporate spies.
Technology is so advanced now,
it's all AI-generated!
Is the audio AI too?
Yun,
there might be some misunderstanding here.
However,
Cheng Yan is definitely unworthy of you.
But our Cheng An is quite good too.
You could consider him!
Cheng Yan,
for what you've done,
I'll never forgive you as long as I live.
Our Song family
has its own pride.
And I have my own bottom line.
I will never let a marriage alliance
ruin me.
Well said, Yun.
Even though she's a girl,
she is fully capable of
inheriting the Song family business.
She is our pride,
not someone to be bullied.
This marriage alliance
is hereby canceled.
Yun,
let's go.
Stop filming!
What are you filming?!
Get lost!
Director Sang, going for lunch?
You guys go ahead.
Okay.
Sang Luo.
Is this your doing again?
I should be the one asking you that.
After all, the ones fighting over a wife
are Youngest Uncle and Second Uncle.
Word has spread everywhere now
that the Cheng family competition is fierce.
It's best if it wasn't you.
Of course it wasn't me.
But I am quite curious.
Youngest Uncle, what does
your current attitude mean?
Did Song Yun reject the marriage alliance,
making you want to marry her so badly?
Do you like her that much?
Whether I like her or not
is my own business.
Everything I do is for Valley Breeze.
Everything else
must make way for it.
Alright.
Got it.
Who was that?
Work.
Are you leaving then?
I'm not leaving.
I promised you
that I'd put you first,
and everything else comes second.
So today,
I'll stay home with you all day.
Liar.
Thanks for your help.
A pleasure doing business.
She's the only precious child of the Song family.
All the future fortune belongs to her.
Once I have her in my hands,
all this future fortune
will belong to me.
It's just a win-win.
Thank you.
I know you like Cheng An,
but I couldn't have him,
and you have no chance either.
Stop your wishful thinking.
Psycho.
After I publicly rejected the marriage alliance,
I didn't expect you to ask me out alone.
To take over Valley Breeze Group,
don't use a marriage alliance as a shortcut.
So,
you have someone else in your heart?
It doesn't matter.
The reason I asked you out this time
is to ask you about Sang Luo.
You know her well, right?
Back then,
I didn't want to follow my parents' plan
to join the family business,
so I sneaked off to volunteer at a hospital.
Sang Luo was the first patient I met.
She was the most optimistic
and kindest girl I had ever met.
Even though it was just a short year,
we became the best of friends.
But then,
my parents tricked me into going abroad,
and I couldn't even give her a proper goodbye.
So,
do you think the current Sang Luo
is the real Sang Luo?
Actually, all these years I've been
keeping an eye out for Sang Luo's whereabouts.
This time,
If I hadn't heard Sang Luo returned,
I'd never agree to the marriage alliance.
But after I came to the Cheng family, I realized...
the person she is now
and the one I remember
are nothing alike.
You mean...